papatek.com 2009-06-20

# Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy**

This Privacy Policy tells you how Papatek.com uses and protects your information.

By using the Papatek.com, you agree to the terms and conditions of the User Agreement, including this Privacy Policy, and you consent to Papatek.com's privacy practices. This includes the use and disclosure of any personal information you have shared with us and its transfer to and storage on our servers in the United States. 

**Collection**

You can browse the Papatek.com without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Certain features and services on the Papatek.com Network require that you register and supply some information that allows us to identify you. We collect some information automatically from your computer while you browse our sites, such as where you go on the Papatek.com Network and what you do there. We collect your IP address, computer and connection information, browser type and version, operating system and platform, the URLs you come from and go to next, and a cookie number. 

When you register on Papatek.com, we collect and store your e-mail address and a password. You can also choose to provide the following personal information:

Member profile information, including first and last name, member name and location   
Fulfillment information, including mailing address and phone number   
Transaction and payment information, including credit card number and billing address   
Other information that allows us to personalize your Papatek.com experience—for example, your filter and profile preferences and the items on your Epinions Wish List 

We may get additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, you might contact Community Care or customer support or respond to a survey, or we might get a third-party complaint about you. 

**Use**

Papatek.com does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. We use the information we collect to:

operate the Papatek.com  
provide you with information and services you request   
customize your experience on the Papatek.com  
communicate with you about your orders, service updates and other administrative issues   
measure and improve our sites and services   
resolve disputes, address complaints and troubleshoot technical problems   
analyze site and user behavior and prepare aggregated reports 

**Security**

Papatek.com uses physical, electronic and administrative safeguards, including advanced firewall and password protection for our databases, designed to protect the security of information. We restrict access to your personal information to employees that need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**General**

We may change this policy from time to time. All amended terms will take effect immediately for new users, and 30 days after they are posted for existing users.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the practices of the Papatek.com, you may e-mail our Privacy Department or contact:

Papatek Inc.  
700 Aldo Ave, Santa Clara, CA 95054  
U.S.A.
